Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-149. Rules. Kanawha and West Virginia Railroad
    - Kanawha and West Virginia Railroad, 1921 (Box 400, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-150. Rules. Kanawha and Michigan Railway
    - Kanawha and Michigan Railway, 1921-1924 (Box 400, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-151. Rules. Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company
    - 1959 Vacation and Holiday Movement, 1949-1960 (Box 400, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 400, Folder 14)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 400, Folder 15)
    - Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company, 1921-1953 (Box 400, Folder 16)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 400, Folder 17)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 400, Folder 18)
    - Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company, 1940-1946 (Box 400, Folder 19)
    - Rules Revision Dispute, 1940-1945 (Box 400, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-152. Rules. Central Weighing and Inspection Bureau
    - Central Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1921-1946 (Box 400, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-153. Rules. Alabama and Vicksburg Railway Company-Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railway Company
    - Alabama and Vicksburg Railway Company-Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railway Company, 1921-1936 (Box 400, Folder 22)
    - Alabama and Vicksburg Railway Company-Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railway Company, 1921 (Box 400, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-154. Rules. Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1941 (Box 400, Folder 24)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1946 (Box 400, Folder 25)
    - Married Women Arbitration Case, 1944 (Box 400, Folder 26)
    - Rules Revision, 1946-1947 (Box 400, Folder 27)
    - Rules Revision, 1945-1946 (Box 400, Folder 28)
    - Company Union Case, 1947-1949 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Panel Board Hearing, 1946 (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Panel Board Hearing, 1946 (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Civil Action, 1963-1966 (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Mediation Case, 1965 (Box 401, Folder 5)
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 401, Folder 6)
    - Appeal: Robert R. Anderson, 1963-1964 (Box 401, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Case, 1962 (Box 401, Folder 8)
    - General, 1956-1962 (Box 401, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 401, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 401, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 401, Folder 12)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1947 (Box 401, Folder 13)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1953-1955 (Box 401, Folder 14)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1954 (Box 401, Folder 15)
    - Married Women Rule, 1942-1952 (Box 401, Folder 16)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 401, Folder 17)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1947-1949 (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1945-1946 (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1947-1952 (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Ore Dock Employees, 1945 (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - General, 1941-1944 (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Married Women Dispute, 1946 (Box 402, Folder 7)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1935-1940 (Box 402, Folder 8)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1921-1923 (Box 402, Folder 9)
    - Ore Dock Employees, 1940-1941 (Box 402, Folder 10)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1933-1935 (Box 402, Folder 11)
    - Hicks' File, 1935 (Box 402, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-155. Rules. Jacksonville Terminal Company
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 402, Folder 13)
    - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1921-1924 (Box 402, Folder 14)
    - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1934-1944 (Box 402, Folder 15)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 402, Folder 16)
    - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1955-1957 (Box 402, Folder 17)
    - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1949 (Box 402, Folder 18)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 402, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-156. Rules. Cupples Station Company
    - Cupples Station Company, 1921-1923 (Box 402, Folder 20)
    - Cupples Station Company, 1935-1943 (Box 402, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-157. Rules. Wabash Railroad Company
    - Piggy-Back Trailers, 1956-1965 (Box 402, Folder 22)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 402, Folder 23)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 402, Folder 24)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1922-1928 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1958 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1957-1962 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - General, 1950-1956 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1946-1950 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1945 (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Acme Fast Freight, 1957-1959 (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Parlor Car Service, 1956-1960 (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1956-1957 (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1940-1944 (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1931-1939 (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1954 (Box 403, Folder 12)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 403, Folder 13)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948 (Box 403, Folder 14)
    - Overtime, 1946-1950 (Box 403, Folder 15)
    - Short-Hour Freight Handlers, 1940-1949 (Box 403, Folder 16)
    - Vacation Dispute, 1944-1946 (Box 403, Folder 17)
    - Overtime, 1943-1946 (Box 403, Folder 18)
    - Wabash Railroad Company, 1935-1936 (Box 403, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-158. Rules. Central Union Depot and Railway Company of Cincinnati
    - Central Union Depot and Railway Company of Cincinnati, 1921 (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-159. Rules. Louisville and Jeffersonville Bridge and Railway Company
    - Louisville and Jeffersonville Bridge and Railway Company, 1921 (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Louisville and Jeffersonville Bridge and Railway Company, 1921 (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-160. Rules. Cincinnati Northern Railroad Company
    - Cincinnati Northern Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Cincinnati Northern Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-161. Rules. Western Railway of Alabama
    - Western Railway of Alabama, 1921-1945 (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-162. Rules. Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 404, Folder 7)
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company, 1941-1954 (Box 404, Folder 8)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 404, Folder 9)
    - Vacations, 1948 (Box 404, Folder 10)
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company, 1936-1940 (Box 404, Folder 11)
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company, 1921-1929 (Box 404, Folder 12)
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company, 1939 (Box 404, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-163. Rules. William Spencer and Son Corporation
    - William Spencer and Son Corporation, 1921 (Box 404, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 279-164. Rules. Chicago, Kalamazoo, and Saginaw Railway
    - Chicago, Kalamazoo, and Saginaw Railway, 1921-1941 (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-165. Rules. Green Bay and Western Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1957 (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad Company, 1921-1942 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad Company, 1934-1936 (Box 405, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-166. Rules. Cincinnati, New Orleans, and Texas Pacific Railway Company
    - Union Shop, 1957 (Box 405, Folder 6)
    - Cincinnati, New Orleans, and Texas Pacific Railway Company, 1923-1939 (Box 405, Folder 7)
    - Cincinnati, New Orleans, and Texas Pacific Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 405, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-167. Rules. Georgia, Florida, and Alabama Railway Company
    - Georgia, Florida, and Alabama Railway Company, 1921 (Box 405, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-168. Rules. Boston, Revere Beach, and Lynn Railroad
    - Boston, Revere Beach, and Lynn Railroad, 1921 (Box 405, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-169. Rules. Davenport, Rock Island, and Northwestern Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 405, Folder 11)
    - Danville and Western Railway. Union Shop, 1957 (Box 405, Folder 12)
    - Danville and Western Railway, 1939-1959 (Box 405, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-170. Rules. Weatherford, Mineral Wells, and Northwestern Railway
    - Weatherford, Mineral Wells, and Northwestern Railway, 1957 (Box 405, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 405, Folder 15)
    - Representation, 1941-1954 (Box 405, Folder 16)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 405, Folder 16a)
  - Sub-Series 279-171. Rules. Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 405, Folder 17)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 405, Folder 18)
    - General, 1956-1962 (Box 405, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway, 1951-1955 (Box 405, Folder 20)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 405, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway, 1944-1950 (Box 405, Folder 22)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway, 1949-1950 (Box 405, Folder 23)
    - Teletype, 1948-1949 (Box 405, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway, 1939-1943 (Box 405, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 279-172. Rules. Northern Pacific Terminal Company
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Company, 1941 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-175. Rules. Peoria Railway Terminal Company
    - Peoria Railway Terminal Company, 1922 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Peoria Railway Terminal Company, 1941-1942 (Box 406, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-176. Rules. Western Stevedore Company
    - Western Stevedore Company, 1921 (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-177. Rules. Grand Central Terminal
    - Mediation Case, 1960-1965 (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case, 1961 (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 406, Folder 7)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 406, Folder 8)
    - Grand Central Terminal, 1957 (Box 406, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-178. Rules. Canadian Pacific Railway
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1946-1956 (Box 406, Folder 10)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1951-1955 (Box 406, Folder 11)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1951-1955 (Box 406, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 406, Folder 13)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1957-1963 (Box 406, Folder 14)
    - General, 1952-1956 (Box 406, Folder 15)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1946-1951 (Box 406, Folder 16)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1947-1949 (Box 406, Folder 17)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1929-1945 (Box 406, Folder 18)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948 (Box 406, Folder 19)
    - Vacations, 1947-1949 (Box 406, Folder 20)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1934-1943 (Box 406, Folder 21)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1922-1928 (Box 406, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-179. Rules. New Orleans and Great Northern Railroad
    - New Orleans and Great Northern Railroad, 1922 (Box 406, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-180. Rules. Columbus and Greenville Railway Company
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 406, Folder 24)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 406, Folder 25)
    - Columbus and Greenville Railway Company, 1944-1956 (Box 406, Folder 26)
    - Military Service, 1942-1947 (Box 406, Folder 27)
    - Vacations, 1940-1945 (Box 406, Folder 28)
    - Columbus and Greenville Railway Company, 1939-1943 (Box 406, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 279-181. Rules. Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad Company, 1943-1944 (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad Company, 1922-1944 (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 407, Folder 6)
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad Company, 1945-1952 (Box 407, Folder 7)
    - Bush Terminal Railroad Company, 1942 (Box 407, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-182. Rules. Bush Terminal Railroad Company
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 407, Folder 9)
    - Vacations, 1946-1948 (Box 407, Folder 10)
    - Bush Terminal Railroad Company, 1923-1942 (Box 407, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 407, Folder 12)
    - Union Shop, 1953-1954 (Box 407, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-183. Rules. Canadian National Railway
    - Canadian National Railway, 1924-1944 (Box 407, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 407, Folder 15)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 407, Folder 16)
    - Black Rock and Buffalo, 1938-1947 (Box 407, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-184. Rules. Charleston Union Station
    - General, 1924-1961 (Box 407, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-185. Rules. Savannah Union Station Company
    - Health and Welfare Joint Movement, 1960 (Box 407, Folder 19)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1957 (Box 407, Folder 20)
    - Savannah Union Station Company, 1936-1950 (Box 407, Folder 21)
    - Savannah Union Station Company, 1945-1947 (Box 407, Folder 22)
    - Savannah Union Station Company, 1924 (Box 407, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-186. Rules. Joliet Union Depot Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 407, Folder 24)
    - Joliet Union Depot Company, 1951-1952 (Box 407, Folder 25)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 407, Folder 26)
    - Rules Revision, 1942-1947 (Box 407, Folder 27)
    - Joliet Union Depot Company, 1924 (Box 407, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 279-187. Rules. Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company
    - Rules Revision, 1963 (Box 407, Folder 29)
    - General, 1956-1963 (Box 407, Folder 30)
    - Mediation Case, 1960-1963 (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case, 1962 (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1959 (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - General, 1944-1955 (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company, 1943-1954 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Emergency Board Report, 1946 (Box 408, Folder 7)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company, 1943-1946 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company, 1932-1943 (Box 408, Folder 9)
    - Teletype, 1948 (Box 408, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 408, Folder 11)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company, 1924-1928 (Box 408, Folder 12)
    - Panel Board Hearing, 1946 (Box 408, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-188. Rules. Chicago Union Station
    - Mediation Case, 1964-1965 (Box 408, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1957-1958 (Box 408, Folder 15)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1952-1957 (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case, 1957-1958 (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1954 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1940-1951 (Box 409, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1951-1953 (Box 409, Folder 6)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 409, Folder 7)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 409, Folder 8)
    - Vacations, 1947 (Box 409, Folder 9)
    - Vacation Dispute, 1944-1947 (Box 409, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1935-1940 (Box 409, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Union Station, 1924-1925 (Box 409, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-189. Rules. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Grand Lodge Office Employees, 1925-1952 (Box 409, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-190. Rules. Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 409, Folder 14)
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company, 1935-1950 (Box 409, Folder 15)
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company, 1936 (Box 409, Folder 16)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 409, Folder 17)
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company, 1925-1926 (Box 409, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-191. Rules. Boston Terminal Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 409, Folder 19)
    - Hours of Service and Working Conditions, 1956-1957 (Box 409, Folder 20)
    - Boston Terminal Company, 1936-1952 (Box 409, Folder 21)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 409, Folder 22)
    - Boston Terminal Company, 1925-1928 (Box 409, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-192. Rules. Portland Terminal Railroad Company
    - Supplemental Pension, 1964-1966 (Box 409, Folder 24)
    - Mediation Case, 1962 (Box 409, Folder 25)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 409, Folder 26)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1958 (Box 409, Folder 27)
    - Portland Terminal Railroad Company, 1926-1930 (Box 409, Folder 28)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 409, Folder 29)
    - Portland Terminal Railroad Company, 1945 (Box 409, Folder 30)
    - General, 1945-1955 (Box 409, Folder 31)
    - General, 1931-1944 (Box 409, Folder 32)
    - Portland Terminal Railroad Company, 1953 (Box 409, Folder 33)
    - Portland Terminal Railroad Company, 1944-1948 (Box 409, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 279-193. Rules. Southern Weighing and Inspection Bureau
    - Southern Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1926-1930 (Box 410, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-194. Rules. Atlanta Terminal Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 410, Folder 2)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 410, Folder 3)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1953 (Box 410, Folder 4)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1956-1958 (Box 410, Folder 5)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1956 (Box 410, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1934-1936 (Box 410, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1939-1953 (Box 410, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1948-1952 (Box 410, Folder 9)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1948 (Box 410, Folder 10)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1946-1954 (Box 410, Folder 11)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company, 1937-1945 (Box 410, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Proceedings, 1936 (Box 410, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-195. Rules. City Bus Company
    - City Bus Company, 1952-1953 (Box 410, Folder 14)
    - City Bus Company, 1941-1953 (Box 410, Folder 15)
    - City Bus Company, 1939 (Box 410, Folder 16)
    - City Bus Company, 1925-1937 (Box 410, Folder 17)
    - General, 1938-1940 (Box 410, Folder 18)
    - City Bus Company, 1952 (Box 410, Folder 19)
    - City Bus Company, 1941-1944 (Box 410, Folder 20)
    - City Bus Company, 1935-1937 (Box 411, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-196. Rules. Union Terminal Company. Dallas
    - Rules Revision, 1962-1963 (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1957 (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1955 (Box 411, Folder 6)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1930-1955 (Box 411, Folder 7)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1946-1961 (Box 411, Folder 8)
    - Arbitration Case, 1946 (Box 411, Folder 9)
    - Arbitration Case, 1946 (Box 411, Folder 10)
    - Arbitration Case, 1946 (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - Arbitration Case, 1946 (Box 411, Folder 12)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1944-1945 (Box 412, Folder 1)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1922-1938 (Box 412, Folder 2)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1940-1945 (Box 412, Folder 3)
    - Union Terminal Company. Dallas, 1956-1960 (Box 412, Folder 4)
    - Clerks. 1958 Rules Movement (Box 412, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case, 1963-1966 (Box 412, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-197. Rules. Southern Pacific Golden Gate Ferries, Limited
    - Southern Pacific Golden Gate Ferries, Limited, 1930 (Box 412, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-198. Rules. Detroit and Toledo Shore Line
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1956-1962 (Box 412, Folder 8)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1941-1955 (Box 412, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 412, Folder 10)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1949-1950 (Box 412, Folder 11)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1956 (Box 412, Folder 12)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1956 (Box 412, Folder 13)
    - Vacations, 1942-1944 (Box 412, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 412, Folder 15)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1942-1946 (Box 412, Folder 16)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1942-1943 (Box 412, Folder 17)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1931-1940 (Box 412, Folder 18)
      1931-1936, 1940.
  - Sub-Series 279-199. Rules.
    - Minnesota and International Railway, 1940 (Box 412, Folder 19)
    - Minnesota and International Railway, 1931-1948 (Box 412, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-200. Rules. Texarkana Union Station Trust
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 412, Folder 21)
    - Texarkana Union Station Trust, 1938-1953 (Box 412, Folder 22)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 412, Folder 23)
    - Vacations, 1944-1946 (Box 412, Folder 24)
    - Texarkana Union Station Trust, 1930-1937 (Box 412, Folder 25)
    - Rules Revision, 1940-1945 (Box 412, Folder 26)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1945 (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Service and Working Conditions (Box 413, Folder 2)
    - Revision Case, 1940 (Box 413, Folder 3)
    - Texarkana Union Station Trust, 1940 (Box 413, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-201. Rules. New York, Westchester, and Boston
    - New York, Westchester, and Boston, 1931 (Box 413, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-202. Rules. Pueblo Union Depot Company
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 413, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 413, Folder 7)
    - Pueblo Union Depot Company, 1951-1953 (Box 413, Folder 8)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 413, Folder 9)
    - Pueblo Union Depot Company, 1932-1952 (Box 413, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1942 (Box 413, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-203. Rules. Union Stock Yards
    - Joint Agency, 1932-1937 (Box 413, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-204. Rules. Tulsa Union Depot
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 413, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 413, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1956 (Box 413, Folder 15)
    - Tulsa Union Depot, 1932-1952 (Box 413, Folder 16)
    - Tulsa Union Depot, 1945 (Box 413, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-205. Rules. Union Inland Freight Terminal
    - Union Shop, 1952 (Box 413, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-206. Rules. Fort Worth Belt Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 413, Folder 19)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 413, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-207. Rules. Cincinnati Union Terminal
    - Union Shop, 1952-1958 (Box 413, Folder 21)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 413, Folder 22)
    - Union Shop, 1952-1953 (Box 413, Folder 23)
    - Union Shop, 1955 (Box 413, Folder 24)
    - Union Shop, 1953 (Box 413, Folder 25)
    - Cincinnati Union Terminal, 1950-1952 (Box 413, Folder 26)
    - Cincinnati Union Terminal, 1933-1952 (Box 413, Folder 27)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 414, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-208. Rules. Panama Railroad
    - Panama Railroad, 1933 (Box 414, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-209. Rules. Monongahela Railroad
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 414, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 414, Folder 4)
    - General, 1933-1955 (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 414, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-210. Rules. Interstate Railroad Company
    - Mediation Case, 1959 (Box 414, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Case, 1959 (Box 414, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-211. Rules. St. Joseph Union Depot Company
    - St. Joseph Union Depot Company, 1951-1959 (Box 414, Folder 9)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1954 (Box 414, Folder 10)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 414, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 414, Folder 12)
    - St. Joseph Union Depot Company, 1944-1950 (Box 414, Folder 13)
    - St. Joseph Union Depot Company, 1934-1946 (Box 414, Folder 14)
    - St. Joseph Union Depot Company, 1944-1945 (Box 414, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-212. Rules. Piedmont and Northern Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 414, Folder 16)
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway Company, 1936-1938 (Box 414, Folder 17)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 414, Folder 18)
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway Company, 1939-1953 (Box 414, Folder 19)
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway Company, 1948 (Box 414, Folder 20)
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway Company, 1934-1936 (Box 414, Folder 21)